<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="https://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="https://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="https://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="https://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="https://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; GMBS Consulting</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/uncategorized/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Insight Management</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 14:57:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/cropped-logo-5-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; GMBS Consulting</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
		<item>
		<title>A Rant About Volunteerism</title>
		<link>/a-rant-about-volunteerism/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[llameadrpc]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 18:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=204</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Volunteering is core to the American experience. People volunteer to help raise a barn. People volunteer to teach Sunday school. People volunteer to fight wars. People volunteer to elect political candidates. Heck, Tennessee bills itself as the Volunteer State. Volunteerism is a dangerous, malignant practice, secondary only to involuntary free work, also known as slavery. &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="/a-rant-about-volunteerism/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "A Rant About Volunteerism"</span></a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Volunteering is core to the American experience. People volunteer to help raise a barn. People volunteer to teach Sunday school. People volunteer to fight wars. People volunteer to elect political candidates. Heck, Tennessee bills itself as the Volunteer State.</p>



<p>Volunteerism is a dangerous, malignant practice, secondary only to involuntary free work, also known as slavery.</p>



<p>Volunteerism devalues the worker and rewards those who excel at conning others into thinking that their &#8220;work is its own reward.&#8221; This is the American version of the German &#8220;Arbeit macht frei&#8221; that adorned the entry to concentration camps. </p>



<p>Volunteerism devalues professionalism, preparation, study, and thoughtful action by saying that anyone can volunteer to do anything, and that years of preparation have no additional value.</p>



<p>Volunteerism hollows out the professional and middle classes of America, leaving only the top class, who gain their material wealth through the very act of stealing others&#8217; work, and the bottom class, who barely survive from the crumbs from their masters&#8217; tables.</p>



<p>Volunteerism is institutionalized abuse of everything  and everyone in our society.</p>



<p>So don&#8217;t ask me for free work. Ask me for a quotation.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>2020 Memphis Poverty Fact Sheet</title>
		<link>/2020-memphis-poverty-fact-sheet/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[llameadrpc]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 19:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[poverty]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=173</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I think that the big takeaway is, although there have been cyclical issues, small ups and downs in poverty in Memphis — 2008 and poverty rises and slightly falls in 2017 and this year — in general it’s pretty flat and resistant to change. It’s small cyclical changes on top of a structural problem. This &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="/2020-memphis-poverty-fact-sheet/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "2020 Memphis Poverty Fact Sheet"</span></a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>I think that the big takeaway is, although there have been cyclical issues, small ups and downs in poverty in Memphis — 2008 and poverty rises and slightly falls in 2017 and this year — in general it’s pretty flat and resistant to change. It’s small cyclical changes on top of a structural problem. This is not about small or even relatively large changes in the national economy. This about the structure of the Memphis economy.</p>



<p><a href="https://bit.ly/2020MemphisPoverty">https://bit.ly/2020MemphisPoverty</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Updated data for Being Sick</title>
		<link>/updated-data-for-being-sick/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[llameadrpc]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 02:37:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Update]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=117</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As of March 15, COPD appears to be less problematic than earlier data suggested. CVD and HTN are still more than sufficient to explain age-dependent mortality.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<a href="/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/Being-Sick-Can-Cost-You-Your-Life-20200315.pdf" class="pdfemb-viewer" style="" data-width="max" data-height="max"  data-toolbar="bottom" data-toolbar-fixed="off">Being-Sick-Can-Cost-You-Your-Life-20200315<br/></a>
<p class="wp-block-pdfemb-pdf-embedder-viewer"></p>



<p>As of March 15, COPD appears to be less problematic than earlier data suggested. CVD and HTN are still more than sufficient to explain age-dependent mortality.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
